altmednetwork.net 2006-10-13

# Alternative Medicine Network Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement**

Alternative Medicine Network has a firm commitment to privacy. 

We ONLY use the information you submit to proces your order and provide you with information regarding shipping and proper product usage or to communicate changes in our product offerings. We will NOT email you with any other company's products... period! We do not now nor will we in the future, sell, rent or otherwise make your personal information available to anyone!

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: altmednework.net. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart. Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (such as email address) and financial information (such as account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is also used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. 

The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor only when necessary. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. 

This site contains links to other sites. Alternative Medicine Network is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

* * *

TOP

home | what's new | products list | become an affiliate  
site map | **our privacy policy** | about us | links we like

© 2003 Alternative Medicine Network
